{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288143605","data":{"timestamp":" 947288143605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288153466","data":{"timestamp":" 947288153465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288155091","data":{"timestamp":" 947288155091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288160251","data":{"timestamp":" 947288160250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288161837","data":{"timestamp":" 947288161836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288164981","data":{"timestamp":" 947288164981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288166535","data":{"timestamp":" 947288166535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288169866","data":{"timestamp":" 947288169866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288171428","data":{"timestamp":" 947288171428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288174164","data":{"timestamp":" 947288174164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288175733","data":{"timestamp":" 947288175733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288181888","data":{"timestamp":" 947288181888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288183453","data":{"timestamp":" 947288183453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288186017","data":{"timestamp":" 947288186017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288187614","data":{"timestamp":" 947288187614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" MPAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288191489","data":{"timestamp":" 947288191489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288193059","data":{"timestamp":" 947288193059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288195975","data":{"timestamp":" 947288195974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288197535","data":{"timestamp":" 947288197535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288200907","data":{"timestamp":" 947288200907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288202463","data":{"timestamp":" 947288202463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" MWEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288206933","data":{"timestamp":" 947288206932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" MWEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288208551","data":{"timestamp":" 947288208550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288210795","data":{"timestamp":" 947288210795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288212417","data":{"timestamp":" 947288212416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" MCHICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288214887","data":{"timestamp":" 947288214886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" MCHICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288216455","data":{"timestamp":" 947288216454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288218646","data":{"timestamp":" 947288218646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288220244","data":{"timestamp":" 947288220243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288224550","data":{"timestamp":" 947288224549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288226134","data":{"timestamp":" 947288226133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288230003","data":{"timestamp":" 947288230002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288231616","data":{"timestamp":" 947288231615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288237825","data":{"timestamp":" 947288237825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288239399","data":{"timestamp":" 947288239399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288243132","data":{"timestamp":" 947288243132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288244683","data":{"timestamp":" 947288244683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288249626","data":{"timestamp":" 947288249626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288251190","data":{"timestamp":" 947288251190"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" MUHOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288259143","data":{"timestamp":" 947288259143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288260742","data":{"timestamp":" 947288260742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288266472","data":{"timestamp":" 947288266472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288268046","data":{"timestamp":" 947288268046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288270420","data":{"timestamp":" 947288270420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288272036","data":{"timestamp":" 947288272036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288276454","data":{"timestamp":" 947288276454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288278001","data":{"timestamp":" 947288278001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288282001","data":{"timestamp":" 947288282001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288283585","data":{"timestamp":" 947288283584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288287661","data":{"timestamp":" 947288287661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288289219","data":{"timestamp":" 947288289219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288293267","data":{"timestamp":" 947288293266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288294897","data":{"timestamp":" 947288294897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288297989","data":{"timestamp":" 947288297989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288299631","data":{"timestamp":" 947288299629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288302117","data":{"timestamp":" 947288302116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288303735","data":{"timestamp":" 947288303734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288306324","data":{"timestamp":" 947288306324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288307951","data":{"timestamp":" 947288307950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288315231","data":{"timestamp":" 947288315230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288316818","data":{"timestamp":" 947288316818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mende"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENDE"," userResponse":" MENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288320236","data":{"timestamp":" 947288320236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mende"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288321797","data":{"timestamp":" 947288321797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahindi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288324551","data":{"timestamp":" 947288324550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahindi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288326166","data":{"timestamp":" 947288326165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288329363","data":{"timestamp":" 947288329363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288329522","data":{"timestamp":" 947288329522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288347414","data":{"timestamp":" 947288347413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947288366732","data":{"timestamp":" 947288366731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_023519"," gameId":" f77b94a0-3cf6-49e9-a8c0-80a214901849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}